# **JASEEL P V**

0567657393

jaseelbavu@gmail.com https://jaseel.in

A suitable position with an organization where I can utilize the best of my skills and abilities that fit to my education, skills and experience a place where an encourage and permitted to be an active participant as well vital contribute on development of the company.

## **SKILLS**

PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, Firebase, Bootstrap, Linux, Rest API, SQL, MySQL, Javascript, CSS, NoSQL, JQuery, Git, Razorpay, Bagisto, Envoyer, Tailwind CSS, Postman, Cashier, Horizon, Passport, Socialite, Telescope, Windows, Bitbucket, gitlab, github

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Palmate Solutions - 09/2019 to 12/2020

Bangalore, Karnataka

- Lead the team to migrate existing and new projects to Laravel framework.
- Providing guidance to the team to learn Laravel framework and with their works.
- Involved in project development from scratch to deployment.
- Develop and worked on both frontend and backend technologies based on provided design.
- Version control system for tracking and managing changes to the project codes.
- Hands on experience with API like REST API, payment API and Google API.
- Work closely with other developers, designers and product manager.
- Design, develop, document, and debug sites and ensure code reuse and organization.
- Works with R&D department to assist in planning and executing new product development.
- Understands the impact of good usability and user experience.
- Ability to admin a Linux server in basic functions for host configuration.

## Co-Founder/Web Developer

Exam Summary - 01/2015 to 05/2017

Nasscom 10,000 startups, Infopark Campus, kakanad, Kerala

- Work closely with other co-founders about the product development and implementation.
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs.
- Conducted target market research to scope out industry competition and identify advantageous trends.
- Help ensure students have a seamless experience across subjects and grade levels.
- Integrate data from various back-end services and databases.
- Create and maintain software documentation.
- Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them into operations and activities.

### **EDUCATION**

## The Oxford College Of Engineering, Bommanahalli

Master of Computer Application

Bangalore, India - 08/2017 to 07/2019

# Assabah Arts And Science College, Valayamkulam

**Bachelor of Computer Application** 

Changaramkulam, India - 08/2013 to 05/2016

## Govt. H S S, Kodumunda

**HSC** - Computer Science

Pattambi, India - 06/2011 to 03/2013

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Marital Status : Single Nationality : Indian

Language Known : English, Malayalam

Address : S/o. Bavu P V

Pulamanthol Valappil House, Chazhiyattiri Post,

Palakkad Dt-Kerala-679535

Passport Number : Normal / R0956090

Visa Status : Visiting Visa Visa Expiry : 05/04/2021